<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<errors>
    <item id="1001" context="">We are unable to process your request. The credit card you selected has been declined. Please select another card. If you have questions about why your credit card was declined, please contact the credit card issuer.</item>
    <item id="1002" context="">We are unable to process your request. The zip code provided does not match our records. Please verify your information and try again.</item>
    <item id="1006" context="">We are unable to process your request. The security code provided does not match our records. Please verify card information and try again.</item>
    <item id="1012" context="">We are unable to process your request. The expiration date provided does not match our records. Please verify card information and try again.</item>
    <item id="3005" context="">We are unable to process your request. The zip code provided does not match our records. Please verify your information and try again.</item>
    <item id="3200" context="">Routing number and Bank account number cannot be the same. Please verify banking information and try again.</item>
    <item id="3307" context="">We are unable to process your request. It looks like you are attempting to make a duplicate payment.</item>
    <item id="3314" context="">We are unable to process your request. Please contact our Customer Care Center at 1-800-685-0123.</item>
    <item id="4330" context="">We are unable to process your request. The routing number provided is not valid. Please verify your information and try again.</item>
    <item id="4331" context="">The bank indicated by the routing number does not allow payments of this type. Please use another payment method.</item>
    <item id="4332" context="">The bank indicated by this routing number is unable to process ACH payments. Please use another payment method.</item>
    <item id="18030" context="">We are unable to process your request. The zip code provided is not valid. Please verify your information and try again.</item>
    <item id="18074" context="">Credit card type is not accepted. You may add a different payment method to your wallet.</item>
    <item id="18077" context="">Card account number has failed validations. Please verify card information.</item>
    <item id="18081" context="">The payment method nickname is invalid. Please re-enter and try again.</item>
    <item id="28003" context="">This payment method already exists in your wallet.</item>
    <item id="28009" context="">We are unable to process your request. The zip code provided is not valid. Please verify your information and try again.</item>
    <item id="19022" context="">The time allowed for processing the card transaction has expired. Please try again.</item>
    <item id="19001" context="">We are unable to process your request. This card account has reached the limit of permitted payments in the last 30 days. Please use a different payment method.</item>
    <item id="19002" context="">We are unable to process your request as you have reached the maximum number of payments permitted. Please contact our Customer Care Center at 1-800-685-0123.</item>
</errors>
