<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<errors>
  <item id="INTHE-0001" context="">We’re sorry, we are unable to process your request at this time. Please try again later or utilize our automated system 1-800-Edison-1 (1-800-334-7661)</item>
  <item id="INVAL-0001" context="">We’re sorry, we are unable to process your request due to incorrect data being entered. Please try again.</item>
  <item id="INVAL-0016" context="">We’re sorry, We are unable to process your request as you have reached the maximum number of payments permitted.</item>
  <item id="INVAL-0017" context="">We’re sorry, We are unable to process your request. Please contact our Customer Care Center at 1-800-Edison-1 (1-800-334-7661) for more information. (Hours of operation: Monday - Friday, 7:00 a.m. to 7:00 p.m CST)</item>
  <item id="INVAL-0018" context="">We’re sorry, We are unable to process your request. Please contact your financial institution for further information.</item>
  <item id="INVAL-0019" context="">Cannot save this wallet item as it already exists!</item>
  <item id="INVAL-0019" context="payment">We’re sorry, We are unable to process your request as the wallet item already exists. Please login to make a payment.</item>
  <item id="INVAL-0022" context="">We’re sorry, We are unable to process your request at this time as your request timed out. Please try again later.</item>
  <item id="INVAL-0024" context="">We’re sorry, we are unable to process your request as it’s a duplicate payment.</item>
  <item id="MPYMT-0009" context="">We’re sorry, we are unable to process your request. The credit card you selected has been declined. Please select another card. If you have questions about why your credit card was declined, please contact the credit card issuer.</item>
  <item id="MPYMT-0011" context="">We're sorry, we can't schedule this payment on the selected date because it exceeds the the number of payments permitted.</item>
  <item id="PYACT-0001" context="">We’re sorry, we are unable to process your request due to incorrect data being entered.Please try again.</item>
  <item id="PYACT-0008" context="">We’re sorry, we are unable to process your request due to incorrect data being entered.Please try again.</item>
</errors>
